Guide to the Nelson Sullivan Video Collection 1976 - 1989 MSS.357
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Video recordings, 1976 - 1988
  - WHISPERS at Pyramid (with Ethel Eichelberger, Tabboo!, Maize, Pet., Ger., etc.), Dean Johnson at Pyramid, 5 Ninth Avenue (with John Epperson to East Village), RuPaul at Jane West Hotel, June 8, 1986; ID: 357.0372 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0372, Box 33, Dvd 357.0372_pt.1, Dvd 357.0372_pt.2)
  - Katia Gallas, December 4, 1988; ID: 357.0373 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0373, Box 33, Dvd 357.0373)
  - Christina's Apartment, Obsessions, November 1988; ID: 357.0374 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0374, Box 33, Dvd 357.0374_pt.1, Dvd 357.0374_pt.2)
    [1] -- Christina's Apartment, 11/11/1988 [2] -- Obsessions, 11/12/1988
  - Susanne Bartsch Copacabana Village People, August 25, 1988; ID: 357.0375 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0375, Box 33, Dvd 357.0375_pt.1, Dvd 357.0375_pt.2)
    Existence and Location of Originals
  - Eddie, Pop Tarts, Albert, Me in a Car, September 15, 1988; ID: 357.0376 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0376, Box 33, Dvd 357.0376)
  - Disco 88 and MTV, Michael Musto, The World, March 29, 1988; ID: 357.0377 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0377, Box 33, Dvd 357.0377)
  - Limelight Da DA, January 20, 1988; ID: 357.0378 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0378, Box 33, Dvd 357.0378)
  - Gay Day Night at Limelight, June 29, 1986; ID: 357.0379 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0379, Box 33, Dvd 357.0379)
  - Dale Livingston and Phil Mealy at the Montclair Art Museum, March 20, 1988; ID: 357.0380 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0380)
  - John Sex with Wendy Wild and Chicklet at Pyramid, Changing of the Guard (part 2), March 1988; ID: 357.0381 (Box 11, Media ID: 357.0381, Box 33, Dvd 357.0381)
    [1] -- John Sex (with Wendy Wild and Chicklet) at Pyramid, 3/9/1988 [2] -- Changing of the Guard (part 2), 3/12/1988
  - My 40th Birthday at Pyramid, March 15, 1988; ID: 357.0382 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0382, Box 33, Dvd 357.0382)
  - Downtown Dukes and Divas, November 15, 1987; ID: 357.0383 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0383, Box 33, Dvd 357.0383)
  - Tom's Party, Lypsinka at La Mama, Albert & Musto, 1986; ID: 357.0384 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0384, Box 33, Dvd 357.0384)
    [1] -- Tom's Party, 5/30/1986 [2] -- Lypsinka at La Mama, Albert & Musto, 6/3/1987
  - The Last Moments of 1986 - Eddie Braddock and Nelson Sullivan, December 31, 1986; ID: 357.0385 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0385, Box 33, Dvd 357.0385)
  - Trans Lux with Eddie and Nozomi, April 25, 1986; ID: 357.0386 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0386, Box 33, Dvd 357.0386_pt.1, Dvd 357.0386_pt.2)
  - Kennon Edit, undated; ID: 357.0387 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0387, Box 33, Dvd 357.0387)
  - Pyramid, Walk with Blackout, June 11, 1986; ID: 357.0388 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0388, Box 33, Dvd 357.0388)
  - My Provincetown, May 19, 1989; ID: 357.0389 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0389, Box 33, Dvd 357.0389)
  - Bunny & Lahoma in blackface at Fag Bar, Fashion Patrol at The World, December 1988; ID: 357.0390 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0390, Box 33, Dvd 357.0390)
    Content warning: Contains blackface
  - Dukes and Divas at New Music Seminar, Now Explosion at Limelight, undated; ID: 357.0391 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0391, Box 33, Dvd 357.0391)
  - Truck Ride to Bentley's, DV8, Copacabana, September 7, 1988; ID: 357.0392 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0392, Box 33, Dvd 357.0392)
    [1] -- Truck Ride to Bentley's, 9/7/1988 [2] -- DV8, 12/29/1988 [3] -- Copacabana, 12/29/1988
  - Albert and Grandma, April 29, 1987; ID: 357.0393 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0393, Box 33, Dvd 357.0393)
    Content warning: Contains racism and xenophobia
  - WHISPERS at Pyramid with Dainty Adora, Keith Brazil, Christina, Tom Lohre Fixes Toilet, 1986-1988; ID: 357.0394 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0394, Box 33, Dvd 357.0394_pt.1, Dvd 357.0394_pt.2)
    [1] -- WHISPERS at Pyramid with Dainty Adora, Keith Brazil, Christina, 9/14/1986 [2] -- Tom Lohre Fixes Toilet, 11/12/1988
  - Continuation of MK Straight to Hell Torso, April 2 and 3, 1988; ID: 357.0395 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0395, Box 33, Dvd 357.0395)
    [1] -- Continuation of April 2 & 3, 1988, 4/2/1988-4/3/1988 [2] -- MK Straight to Hell torso, 4/3/1988
  - Bunny (part 2), Tunnel, Rock and Roll Fag Bar at The World, Nozomi at Pyramid, February 1988; ID: 357.0396 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0396)
    [1] -- Bunny (part 2), 2/3/1988 [2] -- Tunnel, 2/12/1988 [3] -- Rock and Roll Fag Bar at The World, 2/16/1988 [4] -- Nazomi at Pyramid, 2/16/1988
  - Dainty, Albert's Birthday, 1986; ID: 357.0397 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0397, Box 33, Dvd 357.0397)
    [1] -- Dainty, 1/19/1986 [2] -- Albert's Birthday, 11/19/1986
  - Celebrity Club (part 2 of last tape), La Palace at The World, June 1988; ID: 357.0398 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0398, Box 33, Dvd 357.0398)
    [1] -- Celebrity Club (part 2 of last tape), 6/22/1988 [2] -- La Palace at The World, 6/24/1988
  - Celebrity Club #2 Tunnel, April 19, 1988; ID: 357.0399 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0399, Box 33, Dvd 357.0399)
  - Coney Island, Albert on the Street, June 21, 1986; ID: 357.0400 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0400, Box 33, Dvd 357.0400)
  - Celebrity Club, June 15, 1988; ID: 357.0401 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0401, Box 33, Dvd 357.0401)
  - RuPaul (part 2), Rosser Atlanta, Snow at 5 Ninth Avenue, 1986-1989; ID: 357.0402 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0402, Box 33, Dvd 357.0402)
    [1] -- RuPaul (part 2), Rosser Atlanta, 12/11/1986 [2] -- Snow at 5 Ninth Avenue, 2/11/1989
  - Red Zone, Hollywood Twins, Copacabana Fabulous, April 27, 1989; ID: 357.0403 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0403, Box 34, Dvd 357.0403)
  - Church in Kershaw, Jeanie Brewer, February 2, 1989; ID: 357.0404 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0404, Box 34, Dvd 357.0404)
  - Celebrity Club at Tunnel, June 8, 1988; ID: 357.0405 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0405, Box 34, Dvd 357.0405)
  - Arrive in Atlanta, On The American Music Show with Bandages Removed, RuPaul Arrives, February 1989; ID: 357.0406 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0406, Box 34, Dvd 357.0406)
    [1] -- Arrive in Atlanta, 2/6/1989 [2] -- On The American Music Show with Bandages Removed, 2/7/1989 [3] -- RuPaul Arrives, 2/8/1989
  - King and Queen of Downtown, TV, Dainty, Next day - King & Queen of Downtown on TV, Dainty, John Kelly, undated; ID: 357.0407 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0407, Box 34, Dvd 357.0407)
  - Atlanta: RuPaul at Colorbox (part 1), Thrift Store Shopping with Tom Zarrilli, February 10, 1989; ID: 357.0408 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0408, Box 34, Dvd 357.0408)
  - McDonald's Outlaw Party for Frank Roccio with Michael Alig, Floyd's Party, March 18, 1989; ID: 357.0409 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0409, Box 34, Dvd 357.0409_pt.1, Dvd 357.0409_pt.2)
  - Atlanta: Dick and Rupaul and Barker, February 8, 1989; ID: 357.0410 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0410, Box 34, Dvd 357.0410)
  - Grandmama's in Kershaw with Jeanie and Ryan, News Era and Horses, February 3, 1989; ID: 357.0411 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0411, Box 34, Dvd 357.0411)
  - Wigstock Benefit (part 1), May 13, 1987; ID: 357.0412 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0412, Box 34, Dvd 357.0412)
  - Video Titles for Joey Arias by Nelson Sullivan, Dean Johnson and John Sex at Palladium, September 25, 1986; ID: 357.0413 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0413, Box 34, Dvd 357.0413)
  - Celebrity Club (broken tape), June 29, 1988; ID: 357.0414 (Box 21, Media ID: 357.0414)
  - Dirt #2 at Limelight, November 3, 1987; ID: 357.0415 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0415, Box 34, Dvd 357.0415)
  - Atlanta #6, August 18, 1987; ID: 357.0416 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0416, Box 34, Dvd 357.0416)
  - Celebrity Club with Wendy Wild, May 18, 1988; ID: 357.0417 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0417, Box 34, Dvd 357.0417)
  - Pose Arena at Pyramid, Rooftop, East Village, June 25, 1986; ID: 357.0418 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0418, Box 34, Dvd 357.0418)
    [1] -- Pose Arena at Pyramid, 6/25/1986 [2] -- Rooftop, East Village, 6/26/1986
  - Keita in NYC, March 16, 1989; ID: 357.0419 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0419, Box 34, Dvd 357.0419)
  - Downtown Recording Session at 1697 Broadway, April 16, 1988; ID: 357.0420 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0420, Box 34, Dvd 357.0420)
  - Hattie's Birthday, Pyramid to Party, 70's Party at Tunnel, March 1987; ID: 357.0421 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0421, Box 34, Dvd 357.0421)
    [1] -- Hattie's Birthday, Pyramid to Party, 3/30/1987 [2] -- 70's Party at Tunnel, 3/31/1987
  - Photo Session at Liz's for Fenton's "Queens" Article for Graffiti, April 20, 1988; ID: 357.0422 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0422, Box 34, Dvd 357.0422_pt.1, Dvd 357.0422_pt.2)
  - Celebrity Club, RuPaul Leaves for London, July 1988; ID: 357.0423 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0423, Box 34, Dvd 357.0423)
    [1] -- Celebrity Club, 7/27/1988 [2] -- RuPaul Leaves for London, 7/31/1988
  - Christmas, Big Haus, Copa with Lady Hennessy, 1987-1989; ID: 357.0424 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0424, Box 34, Dvd 357.0424_pt.1, Dvd 357.0424_pt.2)
    [1] -- Christmas, 12/25/1987 [2] -- Big Haus, 3/30/1989 [3] -- Copa with Lady Hennessy, 3/30/1989
    Content warning: sexually explicit
  - Atlanta: RuPaul at Colorbox (2nd set), XTC party at Dick's, February 10, 1989; ID: 357.0425 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0425, Box 34, Dvd 357.0425)
  - Pyramid Birthday 7 (tape #2), December 10, 1988; ID: 357.0426 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0426, Box 34, Dvd 357.0426)
  - Mystery Girls, D. Leslie, Fred S., Christina, June 28, 1986; ID: 357.0427 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0427, Box 34, Dvd 357.0427)
  - Atlanta #4 Judy Lahoma Lizette, Sailing in Provincetown, August 1986; ID: 357.0428 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0428, Box 34, Dvd 357.0428)
    [1] -- Judy Lahoma Lizette, 8/10/1986 [2] -- Sailing in Provincetown, 8/15/1986
  - Johnny Brewer, Last Day Home, Trip to Richards and to Atlanta, February 1989; ID: 357.0429 (Box 12, Media ID: 357.0429, Box 34, Dvd 357.0429)
    [1] -- Johnny Brewer, Last Day Home, 2/5/1989 [2] -- Trip to Richards and to Atlanta, 2/6/1989
  - Fetchin Bones at CBGB's (part 1), Pyramid 6th Birthday (2 of 2), December 1987; ID: 357.0430 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0430, Box 34, Dvd 357.0430)
    [1] -- Fetchin Bones at CBGB's (part 1), 12/8/1987 [2] -- Pyramid 6th Birthday (2 of 2), 12/10/1987
  - Julie Jewels Fashion Show, June 15, 1988; ID: 357.0431 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0431, Box 34, Dvd 357.0431)
  - Coney Island with Molli, Trade, Jon, RuPaul, Larry Tee, Rosser - Busted by the Pigs!, July 24, 1988; ID: 357.0432 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0432, Box 34, Dvd 357.0432)
  - WHISPERS at Pyramid, Now Explosion at Pyramid, November 24, 1986; ID: 357.0433 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0433, Box 34, Dvd 357.0433)
  - Christmas Eve with Betty Thom at Sylvia's, Christmas at Home, December 1987; ID: 357.0434 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0434, Box 34, Dvd 357.0434)
    [1] -- Christmas Eve with Betty Thom at Sylvia's, 12/24/1987 [2] -- Christmas at Home, 12/25/1987
  - Atlanta #8 Nancy, August 22, 1987; ID: 357.0435 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0435, Box 34, Dvd 357.0435)
  - Michael Musto Birthday Bananas, Hope Nicholls & Fetchin Bones at Cat Club, December 7, 1987; ID: 357.0436 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0436, Box 34, Dvd 357.0436)
  - Pyramid 6th Birthday (1 of 2), December 10, 1987; ID: 357.0437 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0437, Box 34, Dvd 357.0437)
  - Michael London Benefit at Pyramid, June 3, 1987; ID: 357.0438 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0438, Box 34, Dvd 357.0438)
  - La Palace at Red Zone, Bunny at Mars, Whispers at Paddles, April 16, 1989; ID: 357.0439 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0439, Box 34, Dvd 357.0439)
  - New Year's Eve at Mars, Christina at 5 Ninth- Florent, Revelers, 1988-1989; ID: 357.0440 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0440, Box 35, Dvd 357.0440)
    [1] -- New Year's Eve at Mars, 12/31/1988 [2] -- Christina at 5 Ninth- Florent, 1/6/1989 [3] -- Revelers, 1/7/1989
  - Celebrity Club at Tunnel, June 1, 1988; ID: 357.0441 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0441, Box 35, Dvd 357.0441)
  - Pop Tarts Show, Nancy, 1988-1989; ID: 357.0442 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0442, Box 35, Dvd 357.0442)
    [1] -- Pop Tarts Show, 7/17/1988 [2] -- Nancy, 1988
  - July 4th, 1986 (part 1), July 4, 1986; ID: 357.0443 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0443, Box 35, Dvd 357.0443)
  - Ethyl Eichelberger's Rip Van Winkle, Hair (night #2) at The Saint, Pop Tarts limo, July 18, 1986; ID: 357.0444 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0444, Box 35, Dvd 357.0444_pt.1, Dvd 357.0444_pt.2)
  - Starbooty and German Television, March 2, 1988; ID: 357.0445 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0445, Box 35, Dvd 357.0445)
  - Celebrity Club, Porn Rap Party, May 1988; ID: 357.0446 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0446, Box 35, Dvd 357.0446)
    DVD access copy
    [1] -- Celebrity Club, 5/18/1988 [2] -- Porn Rap Party, 5/25/1988
  - World of Viola and $25,000 at Pyramid, La Palace at Pyramid, January 1988; ID: 357.0447 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0447, Box 35, Dvd 357.0447)
    [1] -- World of Viola and $25,000 at Pyramid, 1/1/1988 [2] -- La Palace at Pyramid, 1/3/1988
  - Celebrity Club, Patrick, Fadia P. Michael Musto & More, July 27, 1988; ID: 357.0448 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0448, Box 35, Dvd 357.0448)
  - RuPaul at time of release party for Michael Musto's book Downtown, May 22, 1986; ID: 357.0449 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0449, Box 35, Dvd 357.0449)
  - Triple Birthday, Pop Tarts party at Tunnel with Albert, November 1987; ID: 357.0450 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0450, Box 35, Dvd 357.0450)
    [1] -- Triple Birthday, 11/17/1987 [2] -- Pop Tarts party at Tunnel with Albert, 11/19/1987
  - Tish and Snooky with Dainty at Limelight, Continued: Eddie, Nick and Chica, December 1986; ID: 357.0451 (Box 21, Media ID: 357.0451, Box 35, Dvd 357.0451)
    [1] -- Tish and Snooky with Dainty at Limelight, 12/12/1986 [2] -- Continued: Eddie, Nick and Chica, 12/3/1986
  - Pop Tarts Party, Albert Crudo and his Pluto shorts, Drag Cat, Floyd's Party (part 2), December 1987; ID: 357.0452 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0452, Box 35, Dvd 357.0452)
    [1] -- Pop Tarts Party, 12/13/1987 [2] -- Albert Crudo and his Pluto shorts, 12/13/1987 [3] -- Drag Cat, 12/15/1987 [4] -- Floyd's Party (part 2), 12/20/1987
  - Celebrity Club #1, April 13, 1988; ID: 357.0453 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0453, Box 35, Dvd 357.0453)
  - Central Park with Blackout, Jon, Larry Tee, RuPaul, Trade, April 17, 1988; ID: 357.0454 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0454, Box 35, Dvd 357.0454)
  - Pop Tarts at The World, January 24, 1988; ID: 357.0455 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0455, Box 35, Dvd 357.0455)
  - Eric Conrad and Vicki at Trixie's, January 7, 1988; ID: 357.0456 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0456, Box 35, Dvd 357.0456)
  - Now Explosion at Pyramid J continued, November 23, 1986; ID: 357.0457 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0457, Box 35, Dvd 357.0457)
  - Julie Is Her Name at Pyramid (take one), February 1, 1988; ID: 357.0458 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0458, Box 35, Dvd 357.0458)
  - Craig Vandenberg and John Sex at Pyramid, January 10, 1987; ID: 357.0459 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0459, Box 35, Dvd 357.0459)
  - Dean Johnson at Palladium, 2500 - Michael Musto Apartment (part 2), 1987; ID: 357.0460 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0460, Box 35, Dvd 357.0460)
    [1] -- Dean Johnson at Palladium, 1/13/1987 [2] -- 2500 - Michael Musto Apartment (part 2), 1/27/1987
  - Information Society at 1018, Hanson Davis, November 7, 1986; ID: 357.0461 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0461, Box 35, Dvd 357.0461)
  - Bitch Off at The World, May 27, 1988; ID: 357.0462 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0462)
    Original Format: Video8mm
  - Paul Litteral & Karen Wedding, October 1, 1988; ID: 357.0463 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0463, Box 35, Dvd 357.0463)
  - Sylvia Miles at 19K, October 2, 1987; ID: 357.0464 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0464, Box 35, Dvd 357.0464)
  - Wigstock #2 (part 2), September 1, 1986; ID: 357.0465 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0465, Box 35, Dvd 357.0465)
  - Celebrity Club #2, Mykul Tronn Birthday, June 1988; ID: 357.0466 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0466, Box 35, Dvd 357.0466)
    [1] -- Celebrity Club #2, 6/8/1988 [2] -- Mykul Tronn Birthday, 6/11/1988
  - Sylvia Miles in Tea with Mommy and Jack, undated; ID: 357.0467 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0467, Box 35, Dvd 357.0467)
  - Celebrity Club Funtone Night with Stephen Saban and The Singing Peek Sisters, July 20, 1988; ID: 357.0468 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0468, Box 35, Dvd 357.0468_pt.1, Dvd 357.0468_pt.2)
  - Joey Heatherrock, Tangella, Eddie, June 4, 1988; ID: 357.0469 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0469, Box 35, Dvd 357.0469)
  - Tish in East Village, Dinah Prince (master edit), June 2, 1986; ID: 357.0470 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0470, Box 35, Dvd 357.0470)
    Content warning: Contains brief nudity
  - Ethel Eichelberger in Klytemnestra, Thanksgiving, 1987; ID: 357.0471 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0471, Box 35, Dvd 357.0471)
    [1] -- Ethel Eichelberger in Klytemnestra, 3/20/1987 [2] -- Thanksgiving, 11/23/1987
  - Fetchin Bones at CBGB's (part 2), Pyramid to Home, La Palace at Siberia, December 1987; ID: 357.0472 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0472, Box 35, Dvd 357.0472)
    [1] -- Fetchin Bones at CBGB's (part 2), 12/8/1987 [2] -- Pyramid to Home, 12/11/1987 [3] -- La Palace at Siberia, 12/12/1987
  - Sylvia Miles in Woodstock edit, Dominique at Liimelight (2800), September 10, 1986; ID: 357.0473 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0473, Box 35, Dvd 357.0473)
  - Celebrity Club with Diamanda Galas, August 3, 1988; ID: 357.0474 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0474, Box 35, Dvd 357.0474)
  - DV8 Roof Party, First Self Video, August 6, 1988; ID: 357.0475 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0475, Box 35, Dvd 357.0475)
  - Christina at The Chelsea, Jayne County at Pyramid, May 27, 1989; ID: 357.0478 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0478)
  - Love Machine #1, June 27, 1989; ID: 357.0479 (Box 13, Media ID: 357.0479, Box 35, Dvd 357.0479)
  - Chameleon Edit, December 8, 1987; ID: 357.0480 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0480, Box 35, Dvd 357.0480)
  - Amnesia at Gay Day Parade, June 25, 1989; ID: 357.0481 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0481, Box 35, Dvd 357.0481)
  - New Camera, Michael Alig Birthday, 1989; ID: 357.0482 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0482, Box 36, Dvd 357.0482)
  - Christina at Chelsea, 5 Ninth Avenue to Florent, Joey Heatherrock, Spank, 1989; ID: 357.0483 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0483, Box 36, Dvd 357.0483)
    [1] -- Christina at Chelsea, 5 Ninth Avenue to Florent, 3/28/1989 [2] -- Joey Heatherrock, Spank, 4/28/1989
  - RuPaul at Hairspray Party, February 22, 1988; ID: 357.0484 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0484, Box 36, Dvd 357.0484)
  - Monologue in Grenwich Village for First Cable Show, Bill Moye & Blackout at Pier (Nelson's last tape), July 1989; ID: 357.0485 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0485, Box 36, Dvd 357.0485)
    [1] -- Monologue in Grenwich Village for First Cable Show, 7/2/1989 [2] -- Bill Moye & Blackout at Pier (Nelson's last tape), 7/3/1989
  - Glen Meadmore at Pyramid, December 6, 1987; ID: 357.0486 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0486, Box 36, Dvd 357.0486)
  - RuPaul Pyramid Show, Grocery (crystal healing) (part2), November 1987; ID: 357.0487 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0487, Box 36, Dvd 357.0487)
  - Lisa E in "Positive Me" #2, Floyd at Milk Bar, October 15, 1988; ID: 357.0488 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0488, Box 36, Dvd 357.0488_pt.1, Dvd 357.0488_pt.2)
  - Me and Eric in East Village, Gaylord at La Roca, June 1987; ID: 357.0489 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0489)
    [1] -- Me and Eric in East Village, 6/10/1987 [2] -- Gaylord at La Roca, 6/20/1987
  - John Sex at Limelight (small room), Specimen at Limelight (main room), Liberty with Tish and Gabriel, July 3, 1986; ID: 357.0490 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0490, Box 36, Dvd 357.0490)
  - Now Explosion at Limelight, May 15, 1986; ID: 357.0491 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0491, Box 36, Dvd 357.0491)
  - Atlanta #3, August 19, 1987; ID: 357.0492 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0492, Box 36, Dvd 357.0492)
  - Sea Cliff, New York, May 10, 1987; ID: 357.0493 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0493, Box 36, Dvd 357.0493)
  - Gullet without the G #1, September 18, 1987; ID: 357.0494 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0494, Box 36, Dvd 357.0494)
  - People Tree Siberia, People Tree at Pyramid, 1987-1988; ID: 357.0495 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0495, Box 36, Dvd 357.0495)
    [1] -- People Tree Siberia, 10/6/1987 [2] -- People Tree at Pyramid, 1/17/1988
  - Walker Art Center at Easter, April 19, 1987; ID: 357.0496 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0496)
  - Liz Party (part 2), Pop Tarts leave Liz's, John Sex's birthday, 1987; ID: 357.0497 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0497, Box 36, Dvd 357.0497)
    [1] -- Liz Party (part 2), 3/29/1987 [2] -- Pop Tarts leave Liz's, 4/11/1987 [3] -- John Sex's birthday, 4/11/1987
  - Limelight Wedding, September 7, 1987; ID: 357.0498 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0498, Box 36, Dvd 357.0498)
  - Rosie Rex at Pyramid, August 1, 1987; ID: 357.0499 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0499, Box 36, Dvd 357.0499)
  - Sunday, Trade, RuPaul head dress, Paris Band ICU, April 1987; ID: 357.0500 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0500, Box 36, Dvd 357.0500)
    [1] -- Sunday, 4/10/1987 [2] -- Trade, RuPaul head dress, Paris Band ICU, 4/12/1987
  - Ballet of Dolls benefit #1 at Pyramid, October 8, 1986; ID: 357.0501 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0501, Box 36, Dvd 357.0501)
  - Paula's Opening in San Francisco, Tour of the Inside of the DV8 Club, and Haight Asbury Visit at Floyd's House where Jimmy Hendix and Janis Joplin lived and nearby acid party, February 14, 1987; ID: 357.0502 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0502, Box 36, Dvd 357.0502)
  - Continuation of La Palace at Pyramid, April 1, 1988; ID: 357.0503 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0503, Box 36, Dvd 357.0503)
    [1] -- Continuation of April 1, 1988, 4/1/1988 [2] -- La Palace at Pyramid, 4/2/1988
  - Pop Tarts Palladium Party, March 4, 1987; ID: 357.0504 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0504, Box 36, Dvd 357.0504)
  - DeeLite, John Sex, Wendy Wild at Pyramid, MTV at Tunnel, April 1, 1988; ID: 357.0505 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0505, Box 36, Dvd 357.0505)
  - New York to Atlanta, RuPaul at Weekends, Sunset, Alice Bost, Provincetown roof, George Johnson, August 1986; ID: 357.0506 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0506, Box 36, Dvd 357.0506)
    [1] -- New York to Atlanta, RuPaul at Weekends, 8/2/1986 [2] -- Sunset, Alice Bost, Provincetown roof, George Johnson, 8/16/1986
  - Nozomi and John, Flloyd's party at Times Square, December 1987; ID: 357.0507 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0507, Box 36, Dvd 357.0507)
    [1] -- Nasomi and John, 12/12/1987 [2] -- Flloyd's party at Times Square, 12/20/1987
  - Albert to Pop Tarts to Limelight with Alexis and Karon, Dawn Huston, 1986; ID: 357.0508 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0508, Box 36, Dvd 357.0508)
    [1] -- Albert to Pop Tarts to Limelight with Alexis and Karon, 11/27/1987 [2] -- Dawn Huston, 12/7/1987
  - Michael Musto's apartment and Trivia with Lisa, McA, James St. James (part 1), January 27, 1987; ID: 357.0509 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0509, Box 36, Dvd 357.0509)
  - Disco 88 at Pyramid, March 8, 1988; ID: 357.0510 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0510, Box 36, Dvd 357.0510)
  - My Birthday, March 15, 1987; ID: 357.0511 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0511, Box 36, Dvd 357.0511)
  - Celebrity Club, August 17, 1988; ID: 357.0512 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0512, Box 36, Dvd 357.0512)
  - Lady Clare in San Francisco, Walk in San Francisco, February 1987; ID: 357.0513 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0513, Box 36, Dvd 357.0513)
    [1] -- Lady Clare in San Francisco, 2/14/1987 [2] -- Walk in San Francisco, 2/15/1987
  - Sunday with Lady Clare, Wigstock III (part 1), September 1987; ID: 357.0514 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0514, Box 36, Dvd 357.0514_pt.1, Dvd 357.0514_pt.2)
    [1] -- Sunday with Lady Clare, 9/6/1987 [2] -- Wigstock III (part 1), 9/7/1987
  - Pyramid #2: Sister Dimension, John Kelly, Alexis, Michael London, Tom Rubnitz videos, Bunny, Mr. Fashion, October 8, 1986; ID: 357.0515 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0515, Box 36, Dvd 357.0515)
  - Apollo Mystery Concert 2 (part 2; speed edit), March 13, 1988; ID: 357.0516 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0516, Box 36, Dvd 357.0516)
  - Celebrity Club #4 at Tunnel, May 4, 1988; ID: 357.0517 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0517, Box 36, Dvd 357.0517)
  - Tunnel with John Sex, Alexis, Bunny, RuPaul, Craig Vandenberg, March 24, 1988; ID: 357.0518 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0518, Box 36, Dvd 357.0518)
  - Tony Cimino/Neil, June 4, 1988; ID: 357.0519 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0519, Box 23, Dvd 357.0519)
  - My Birthday (part 2 by Guy), Rhonda's Birthday, March 1987; ID: 357.0520 (Box 14, Media ID: 357.0520, Box 23, Dvd 357.0520)